(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-27T14:14:28.960196",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were there,
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
I want to thank you over and over
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
and tell you right now!
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's hop in!
ridin' on dreams
yeah！！
Yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Whoop-oh-oh...
ああ 小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような
into feelings we couldn't even imagine,
想いになったんだよ
it has grown.
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら 絆が舵になる
No matter how often we get lost, our bond is our rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ 吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
We'll blow away even the slightest bit of anxiety!
果てしない旅路を今 軽いでる途中に
Right now, as we lightly tread this endless journey,
困難もあるでしょう それも力に変えて
there may be hardships, but we'll turn them into strength
一緒に進むんだよ！
and move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were there,
ねえ、夢では終えられない
hey, we can't let it end just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう “らしく”輝いていたい
Let's ride over the rough waves and shine true to ourselves.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねえ、宝物だから
hey, is my greatest treasure,
手を取り合い 声かけ合って 地図など無い未知の世界で
so holding hands and calling out to each other, let's keep going into an uncharted world without a map!
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep going further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Whoop-oh-oh...
急な風が僕らの 行く先乱そうとも
Even if sudden winds try to disrupt our path,
あの日誓ったんだよ 覚悟は揺るがない
we swore on that day our resolve will never waver.
ちゃんとしなくちゃ！って背中 明日への橋になる
"We've gotta do it right!"—that push on the back becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしないとね “あたりまえ”はないから
We have to cherish things more, because nothing is guaranteed.
小さな船から始まるストーリー どこから始めたらいいかもがいて
A story starting from a small boat, struggling over where to begin,
少しずつね輪になって見つけた 何にも代えられない夢だ
little by little forming a circle and finding a dream irreplaceable by anything else!
wow oh oh oh oh oh 未完成も愛して
Wow oh oh oh oh oh, loving even the incomplete,
wow oh oh oh oh oh 想いは一つだ
wow oh oh oh oh oh, our feelings are one.
wow oh oh oh oh oh 僅かな希望でも
Wow oh oh oh oh oh, even with just a glimmer of hope,
僕と君でずっと 馬鹿にされても信じたい！
you and I will keep believing, even if we are laughed at!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" isn't enough,
ねえ、想いが溢れ出しちゃうんだよ
hey, my feelings are overflowing,
ずっと一緒だよ！
we'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were there,
ねえ、夢では終えられない
hey, we can't let it end just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう “らしく”輝いていたい
Let's ride over the rough waves and shine true to ourselves.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねえ、宝物だから
hey, is my greatest treasure,
手を取り合い 声かけ合って 地図など無い未知の世界で
so holding hands and calling out to each other, let's keep going into an uncharted world without a map!
まだまだ行けるから！
Because we can still go further!
ひとりじゃない
You're not alone,
何度でも立ち上がってさ
stand up no matter how many times,
笑い合っていたい
and let's laugh together!
願いだってさみんなで、さあ！
That's our wish, everyone, come on!
手を繋いで 想像も超えて まだまだ行こう！
Holding hands, going beyond imagination, let's keep going further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Whoop-oh-oh...
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" many times
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's ride!
ridin' on dreams
yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような
To feelings that I couldn't have imagined
想いになったんだ
I'm so excited, it won't stop!
わくわく止まらない！
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が舵になる
our bond becomes the rudder
ちょっとの不安だってさ
We can blow away even a little bit of anxiety
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
果てない旅路を今
The endless journey we are on now
凌いでる途中に困難もあるでしょ
There might be difficulties on our way
それも力に変えて
Let's turn that into power
一緒に進むんだよ！
and move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, I don't want to end it in a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough seas together
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to keep shining "like myself"
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I met you
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, it's a treasure
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Taking each other's hands, calling out to each other
地図など無い未知の世界で
In an unknown world with no map
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep going!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden wind tries to disturb
行く先乱そうとも
our path
あの日誓ったんだ
I swore that day
覚悟は揺るがない
My determination will not waver
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
Your back, saying "I have to do it properly",
明日への橋になる
becomes a bridge to tomorrow
もっと大事にしなきゃね
I have to cherish it more
“あたりまえ”は無いから
Because there's no "taken for granted"
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story that starts from a small boat
どっから始めたらいいかもがいて
Struggling with where to start
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
Little by little, we formed a circle and found it
何にも代えられない夢だ
It's a dream that cannot be replaced by anything
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Love the unfinished too
wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
Our feelings are one
wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even with a little bit of hope
僕と君でずっと
With you and me, forever
馬鹿にされてもいい
Even if we are laughed at
信じたい！
I want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" is not enough
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, I don't want to end it in a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough seas together
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to keep shining "like myself"
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I met you
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, it's a treasure
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Taking each other's hands, calling out to each other
地図など無い未知の世界で
In an unknown world with no map
まだまだ行けるから！
Because we can still go!
ひとりじゃない
I'm not alone
何度でも立ち上がってさ
Standing up again and again
笑い合っていたい
I want to laugh together
願いだってさみんなで、さあ！
Let's make our wishes come true together!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Holding hands, going beyond our imagination
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep going!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, I don't want to end it in a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough seas together
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to keep shining "like myself"
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I met you
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, it's a treasure
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Taking each other's hands, calling out to each other
地図など無い未知の世界で
In an unknown world with no map
まだまだ行けるから！
Because we can still go!
ひとりじゃない
I'm not alone
何度でも立ち上がってさ
Standing up again and again
笑い合っていたい
I want to laugh together
願いだってさみんなで、さあ！
Let's make our wishes come true together!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Holding hands, going beyond our imagination
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep going!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here.
ねぇ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, saying "thank you" over and over
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう!
Come on, let's hop aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah!!
wow oh oh…
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような
Into feelings we couldn't
想いになったんだ
even imagine, it grew.
わくわく止まらない!
Our excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we got lost,
絆が舵になる
our bond becomes the rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
we'll blow it all away!
果てしない旅路を今
This endless journey right now
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
As we row along, there are bound to be hardships,
それも力に変えて
but turning even those into strength,
一緒に進むんだよ!
we'll press forward together!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here.
ねぇ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, we won't let it end just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride over the rough waves together.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine in my own way.
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねぇ、宝物だから
Hey, is my treasure.
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an uncharted world with no map,
まだまだ行こう!
let's go even further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Even if sudden winds
行く先乱そうとも
try to disrupt our path ahead,
あの日誓ったんだ
we swore on that day
覚悟は揺るがない
our resolve will not waver.
ちゃんとしなくちゃ!って背中
A back saying 'We've gotta do it right!'
明日の橋になる
becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしないとね
We've got to cherish it even more,
“あたりまえ”はないから
because nothing is taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small boat,
どこから始めたらいいかもがいて
struggling over where to begin,
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
bit by bit, forming a circle, we found
何にも代えられない夢だ
a dream that nothing else can replace.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Love our unfinished selves too
wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
Our feelings are one
wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even with just a slender hope,
僕と君でずっと
you and I will always
馬鹿にされても
Even if we're mocked,
信じたい!
we want to believe!
ねぇ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, 'thank you' isn't enough
ねぇ、想いが溢れ出しちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing.
ずっと一緒だよ!
We'll be together forever!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here.
ねぇ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, we won't let it end just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride over the rough waves together.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine in my own way.
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねぇ、宝物だから
Hey, is my treasure.
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an uncharted world with no map,
まだまだ行けるから!
we can still go further!
ひとりじゃない
You're not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
No matter how many times you get back up,
笑い合っていたい
I want us to laugh together.
願いだって みんなで、さあ!
Even our wishes, everyone, come on!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Holding hands, going beyond imagination,
まだまだ行こう!
let's go even further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here.
ねぇ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, we won't let it end just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride over the rough waves together.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine in my own way.
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねぇ、宝物だから
Hey, is my treasure.
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an uncharted world with no map,
まだまだ行けるから!
we can still go further!
ひとりじゃない
You're not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
No matter how many times you get back up,
笑い合っていたい
I want us to laugh together.
願いだって みんなで、さあ!
Even our wishes, everyone, come on!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Holding hands, going beyond imagination,
まだまだ行こう!
let's go even further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were there
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, thanking you over and over
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう！
Now let's jump aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah！！
Yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey！！ hey！！
Hey!! Hey!!
yeah！！
Yeah!!
ああ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような想いになったんだ
It became feelings I couldn't imagine
わくわく止まらない！
Excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we got lost
絆が舵になる
Our bonds become the rudder
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little anxiety
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
We'll blow it all away
果てない旅路を今
Now on this endless journey
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
There must be hardships as we row
それも力に変えて
Turning those into strength too
一緒に進むんだよ！
We'll move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were there
ねえ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, I won't let it end as a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride over the rough waves too
“らしく”輝いていたいたい
I want to shine "like myself"
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, is my treasure
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other
地図など無い未知の世界で
In an unknown world with no map
まだまだ行こう！
We can still go further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey！！ hey！！
Hey!! Hey!!
yeah！！
Yeah!!
急な風が僕らの行く先乱そうとも
Even if sudden winds try to disrupt our destination
あの日誓ったんだ
We swore that day
覚悟は揺るがない
Our resolve won't waver
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
Telling ourselves "We've gotta do it right!"
明日への橋になる
Becomes a bridge to tomorrow
もっと大事にしないとね
We've gotta cherish it even more
“あたりまえ”はないから
Because nothing is "taken for granted"
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small ship
どこから始めたらいいか迷って
Wondering where we should start
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
We slowly formed a circle and found it
何にも代えない夢だ
It's a dream that cannot be replaced by anything
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Love the incomplete too
wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
Our feelings are one
wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even with just a sliver of hope
僕と君でずっと
You and I will always
馬鹿にされても
Even if we get mocked
信じたい！
We want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, thank you isn't enough
ねえ、想いが溢れきちゃうんだよ
Hey, our feelings are overflowing
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll always be together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were there
ねえ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, I won't let it end as a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride over the rough waves too
“らしく”輝いていたいたい
I want to shine "like myself"
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, is my treasure
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other
地図など無い未知の世界で
In an unknown world with no map
まだまだ行けるから！
Because we can still go further!
ひとりじゃない
You're not alone
何度でも立ち上がって
Stand up no matter how many times
笑い合っていたい
I want us to laugh together
願いだってさみんなで、さあ！
Let's make our wish come true together, come on!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Holding hands and going beyond imagination
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep going!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey！！ hey！！
Hey!! Hey!!
yeah！！
Yeah!!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were there
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, thanking you over and over
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう！
Now let's jump aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah！！
Yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey！！ hey！！
Hey!! Hey!!
yeah！！
Yeah!!
ああ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような想いになったんだ
It became feelings I couldn't imagine
わくわく止まらない！
Excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we got lost
絆が舵になる
Our bonds become the rudder
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little anxiety
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
We'll blow it all away
果てない旅路を今
Now on this endless journey
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
There must be hardships as we row
それも力に変えて
Turning those into strength too
一緒に進むんだよ！
We'll move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were there
ねえ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, I won't let it end as a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride over the rough waves too
“らしく”輝いていたいたい
I want to shine "like myself"
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, is my treasure
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other
地図など無い未知の世界で
In an unknown world with no map
まだまだ行こう！
We can still go further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey！！ hey！！
Hey!! Hey!!
yeah！！
Yeah!!
急な風が僕らの行く先乱そうとも
Even if sudden winds try to disrupt our destination
あの日誓ったんだ
We swore that day
覚悟は揺るがない
Our resolve won't waver
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
Telling ourselves "We've gotta do it right!"
明日への橋になる
Becomes a bridge to tomorrow
もっと大事にしないとね
We've gotta cherish it even more
フブミオは夫婦
Fubuki and Mio are a married couple
いつもありがとう！YAGOO いつもたくさんの元気を...
Thank you always, YAGOO! Thank you for all the energy...
大神ミオ 3D
Ookami Mio 3D
ねねち 愛してる
I love you, Nenechi!
エリート巫女 さくらみこ
Elite Shrine Maiden Sakura Miko
AUTO FISTER
Shishiro Botan
ホロメンが好きだ！！ ホロリスも好きだ！！
I love Holomembers!! I love Holofans too!!
フブちゃん痛車で来た！！ from 高知
Came in Fubu-chan's itasha!! from Kochi
Oozora Subaru
Get Botan a Jetpack
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here.
ねぇ、ありがとうを何度も
Saying thank you over and over,
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
wanting to tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう！
Now let's climb aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah!!
たどたどしく描いては
Falteringly, we sketched it out,
どこか少し笑ってた未来予想図
a blueprint of the future with a faint smile.
あの日の続きを見よう
Let's see what lies beyond that day.
ペタペタ繋いで風も着こなして
Stitching it together, weathering the wind,
扉を叩いて連れてくよ
I'll knock on the door and take you along.
どんなことはきっと一緒なら叶えていける
Whatever it is, together we can make it come true.
鳴りやまない希望求めるほら
Seeking unending hope, look—
鳴りやまない聞こえてる歌声
unending, the singing voice can be heard.
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here,
ねぇ、夢では終わらせない
hey, we won't end it as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride over the rough waves too.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine \"as I am\".
ねぇ、君と出会えたことが
Hey, meeting you
ねぇ、宝物だから
hey, is my treasure.
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an uncharted world with no map,
まだまだ行けるから！
we can still go further!
ひとりじゃない
You are not alone,
何度でも立ち上がってさ
standing up over and over,
笑い合っていたい願いだって
hoping to keep smiling together.
みんなで、さあ！
Everyone, now!
好きなことをしていたい
I want to do what I love
愚か者でいいじゃない
It's fine to be a fool
羽ばたく君を追いかけた夏に
In the summer I chased you as you spread your wings
シュビデュビデュビデュビ
Shubi dubi dubi dubi
ずっといたいドゥビドゥワ
I want to stay forever, do-be-do-wop
パッパ パラダイス
Pappa Paradise
期待しちゃうとガッカリするかも
If I hope for too much, I might be disappointed
それがどうした？次の楽しみが
But so what? The next fun thing
ドアの向こうで待ってるよ
is waiting on the other side of the door
斜め掛けしたスイカのバッグに
In my diagonally hung watermelon bag
大事なものがいっぱい詰まっていて
are packed lots of important things
ラララララ
Lalalalala
降り積もる道しるべはまだ
The piled-up guideposts are still
ラララララ
Lalalalala
覚えている？揺れてる歌
Do you remember? The swaying song
ぬくもりに手を伸ばしたら
When I reached out my hand for warmth
足跡に虹がかかる
a rainbow arches over my footprints
きっと捕える口づかるステージ
I'll surely capture and hum it on stage
はっきりと記した場所へ運ぶ
Carrying me to the clearly marked place
約束を輝きに乗せて世界へ
Carrying our promise shining into the world
響けメロディ いつまでも
Resound, melody, forever and ever
君と踏み出したあの1歩 あの瞬間が
That first step I took with you, that very moment
宝物が背中を押す 今
Treasure pushes me forward, right now
歩いて話して笑って 前を向くんだ
Walking, talking, laughing, looking ahead
色褪せないまま
Without ever fading
混ざり合う僕らの声 ほら
Our voices blend together, see?
聞こえてる？響いてる歌
Can you hear it? The swaying song
パッパ パラダイス
Pappa Paradise
ハモニカ 重ねた言葉 鮮やかな日々の向こう
Harmonica, overlapping words, beyond those vivid days
ずっと君と彩るよ ストーリー
I'll keep coloring the story with you forever
はっきりと結んだ夢が 空へ駆けてゆく
The dream we clearly tied together dashes toward the sky
きらめきに乗せて あなたへ 世界へ
Carrying it on a sparkle, to you, to the world
響けメロディ ここまでも
Resound, melody, even up to here
パレ パレ パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it sparkles!
呼び合う声を合図に
Using our calling voices as a signal
パレ パレ パレ 探しに行く
Parade, parade, parade, we're going to search
ずっとは何なのって
Asking what 'forever' really means
ひとりごと続いた
Monologues continued
ただ始まりたくて走った
I just wanted it to start, so I ran
遠く二人になった
Far away, we became two
それはまぶしすぎた名前
That name was far too dazzling
それは優しすぎる思い出
That memory was far too gentle
もっと近づけと手を伸ばした 思いがけず結び合った
I reached out my hand to get closer, and unexpectedly we bonded
ほら 今マイホームは本物になった
Look, now my home has become real
パレ パレ パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it sparkles!
愛しいとしのつれだって
In the company of our beloved ones
おいで 風夢跳び立てるさ
Come on, wind, we can leap into our dreams!
ささやかな違和感は 終わりなききざし
A faint sense of discomfort is an endless sign
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
I can hold my head high that I found you
ここから これから 眩いパレ パレ
From here, from now on, a dazzling parade, parade
まだ頼りない予感を
A premonition still unreliable
歌を恥ずかしくなんてないよ
There's nothing to be ashamed of in singing
誰も溶けないイマジナリー
An imaginary world no one can melt
いつかまた会えるイマジナリー
An imaginary world where we can meet again someday
あの日に...
To that day...
ゼロに始まったストーリー
The story that started from zero
数えきれないことの数えるような思い出じゃないさ
It's not memories you can just count up,
ほら今僕らを一つと呼ぼう
Look, now let's call ourselves as one
パレ・パレ・パレ・美しかったよ
Parade, parade, parade, it was so beautiful
許し合える刹那 夜はきらめく
Moments of forgiveness, the night sparkles
雨、晴れ、カレイド またとない空
Rain, shine, kaleidoscope, a sky like no other
相応しい旅路とは君と在ることさ
A fitting journey is being by your side
君と在ることなんだ
It's about being with you
「ただいま」を聞けば
When I hear "I'm home"
「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
I shout "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that just natural?
パレ・パレ・パレ・輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, shining bright!
暗がりを満たすのは君だ 僕だ!
What fills the darkness is you, it's me!
パレ・パレ・パレ・輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, shining bright!
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
Bring along both regrets and love
風、夢、羽飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, feathers, you can take flight
ささやかな祈りは光 終わりなき兆し
Quiet prayers are light, endless signs
君と飛び込んでゆく
Jumping in together with you
素敵なスタートさここからこれから
A wonderful start, from here on out
our bright parade, parade!
描いた未知のキャンバス 重ねる景色
An unpainted canvas of the unknown, overlapping landscapes
繋いでみて 繰り返しテイク衝動
Connecting them, repeating action and impulse
揺らいだ目の前に広がる世界
The world spreading out before my wavering eyes
星屑のメロディ 歌に乗せた
Stardust melody set to song
クラっと鮮やかに眩しそうに 駆け抜けるよ スターライト
Dizzily, vividly, dazzlingly, running through, starlight!
we can fly そう僕らは
We can fly, yes, we are
いつしか夢の中 引かれて
Attracted into a dream before we knew it
ただがむしゃらに走り続けたよ
We just kept running recklessly
無限の宇宙に響いたキミを照らす声は
The voice illuminating you echoing in the infinite universe
どこへだってきらり 飛んでいけるんだ
Can sparkle and fly anywhere
愉快な仲間と歩いた非日常
The extraordinary walked with joyful companions
掴んでみて 指先の一等星
Try grasping it, the first-magnitude star at your fingertips
滲んでいく目の前に広がった限界は
The limits spreading out before my blurring eyes
皆の手重ねて ぶっ壊して
Overlapping everyone's hands, breaking them down
吸い込まれそうな夜空を見上げて
Looking up at the night sky that seems to suck you in
今叫ぶよ スターライト
Now shouting out, starlight!
i wanna be そう僕らは
I wanna be, yes, we are
いつでも側で笑い合って
Always smiling together by each other's side
あふれる声が遠くこだまする
Overflowing voices echoing far away
願いの欠片を灯したキミの腕を引いて
Pulling your arm that lit up the fragments of wishes
どこへだってきらり 飛んでいけるんだ
Can sparkle and fly anywhere
ちょっと不安な日も
Even on days a bit uneasy
魔法をかけて ハッピー
Cast a spell, happy!
百人力で乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome it with superhuman strength
アクアブルーに染まる
Dyed in aqua blue
大空にめがけた 鼓動が弾んでく
Heartbeat bounding toward the vast sky
we can fly そう僕らは
We can fly, yes, we are
この日をずっと待ってたんだ
We've been waiting for this day all along
まだ覚めないで
Don't wake up yet
starlight 僕らは止まらない
Starlight, we won't stop
その光が消える1秒前まで走り続けるよ
Continuing to run until one second before that light fades
無限の宇宙に響いたキミを照らす声は 強く抱いてきらり輝いてゆけ
The voice illuminating you echoing in the infinite universe, hold it tight and shine brilliantly
窓を見ている 雨がほほを伝う
I'm looking at the window, the rain runs down my cheek
空を見ている 雲がこころ覆う
I'm looking at the sky, the clouds cover my heart
もう夢を見ることを忘れていた
I had already forgotten how to dream
水晶宮には太陽が輝かない
The sun does not shine in the Crystal Palace
景色はモノクロームに 季節の風は機械仕掛けの
The scenery is monochrome, the seasonal wind is clockwork
ガス灯が夜に揺れてわたしを見失う
The gaslight sways in the night, and I lose sight of myself
流れる時間は明日へとからみあう 赤い糸はデラシネ
The flowing time is intertwined with tomorrow, the red thread is deraciné
人生は理不尽だけれど受け入れてしまえば涙は止まる
Life is unreasonable, but if you accept it, the tears will stop
青空を見上げて少し微笑む
Looking up at the blue sky, I smile a little
小さな喜びがこころを満たしている
Small joys fill my heart
でもひとりであるのは辛い
But it's hard to be alone
青空を見上げて空想しましょう
Looking up at the blue sky, let's fantasize
わたしのすべてをああ抱きとめる愛しい人を
About the beloved person who holds all of me
青空を見上げていつかひとりで
Looking up at the blue sky, someday alone
立ち上がる勇気を少しだけ下さい
Please give me a little courage to stand up
I'm way too cool for this
I do my thing, no rules for this
I get that bag it's lucrative, you curious?
Look closer, it's so obvious
How I can make a scene
Jump with my energy
I'll make you scream it loud, loud, loud
Serve it up on a platter, leave no crumbs
Ate it up, that's just my ego
It's your attention that I crave on the stage, I feel it
Pumping through my veins, comin' at you right now
It's my, it's my, it's my, it's my
It's my, it's my ego-go-go
Living for your applause
I'll dance on either way
Fueling up my fantasy, I'm breaking through
It's just my ego-go-go
I'm doing what they thought I couldn't do
Xoxo, ego
The rise and fall
Of a popstar, oh
Yuh, I'm on an ego trip
No mirage, all real, it ain't no trick
I don't hold my tongue, I know I'm it
I'm your favorite's favorite, I'm that bitch
Tabloids say, "I'm conceited," and they're right
Ain't no shame, either way they're gonna write
"She's so explicit," but stay in my mentions, huh?
Got your attention, baby, that's show business
It's my, it's my, it's my, it's my
It's my, it's my ego-go-go
Living for your applause
I'll dance on either way
Fueling up my fantasy, I'm breaking through
It's just my ego-go-go
I'm doing what they thought I couldn't do
Xoxo, ego
They say I'm a show off
Don't like it? Tough luck
Xoxo, ego
Ah, ah
That's just my ego
Xoxo
飛び跳ねていこう！
Let's jump higher!
今日のフェスも盛り上がっていくぞ！
Let's make today's fest even more exciting!
現地のみんなもネットで見てるみんなもたくさん楽しんでってね！
Everyone here, and everyone watching online, have lots of fun!
いくぞ！
Let's go!
照らす星屑中 闇夜みたいだ
I want to pierce through the darkness to the shining stars
輝く星までのびる 匂いますだ
Extending all the way to the galaxy, I feel so happy
大幸福 目出度いだ 揺れながら暇を もてあましている
Overwhelmed with happiness, I can hold my tears back
私 まった昨日と同じ形して固まってる
I'm still frozen in the exact same shape as yesterday
ねえ寒くても前に進めないの
Why can't I move forward even when I'm freezing?
それぐらいさしてよ 悲しい終わり方
At least let it end with some sorrow...
da-da-la-la, da-la dark ra-pa-pan-pan-pan
(you will want it more, want it more)
ra-pa-pan-pan-pan (ayy)
(you will love it now, love it)
ra-pa-pan-pan
風穴開けたんだ
I blew a hole right through,
支配は始まった
dominion has begun.
息はもう掛けたの
I've already breathed on you,
but you don't know 自覚ないはずよ
but you don't know, you have no idea.
(huff-n-puff)
抑え切れない自力
A self-power I can't quite contain,
制御不能なpower
an uncontrollable power.
捕まえてみなよ 影形もないmy heart
Try and catch my heart that has no shadow or shape!
(i'm so crazy, crazy in love)
半信半疑な素振りはno-no
Half-doubting gestures are a no-no.
心に従って忠誠心見せてよ 今こそ
Follow your heart and show your loyalty right now!
baby, don't let me down
ra-pa-pan-pan-pan (ayy)
gotta be kidding me クセになるでしょ？
Gotta be kidding me, it's getting addictive, right?
ra-pa-pan-pan-pan (ayy)
no love's killing me 足りないのよ oh no
No love's killing me, it's not enough, oh no!
yes! dark breath
感じるでしょ 革命的な存在を
can you feel it? This revolutionary existence!
it's god's breath 滞る感情 吹き払って
It's God's breath, blowing away stagnant emotions.
浅はかな言葉 建前並べて
Superficial words, lining up facades,
何も無いことぐらい baby, i know
as if nothing is there, baby, I know.
ほら 図星でしょ？
Look, I hit the nail on the head, right?
(huff-n-puff)
枯れゆくこと受け入れた 鮮やかなflower
A vibrant flower that accepted withering away,
知りながら贈る笑顔に潜む姿
hiding in the smile given while knowing.
(really hate it, hate its smile)
心侵食される前に その身を預けて
Before your heart is invaded, entrust your body
目覚めさせるのよ 永遠に
and awaken it for eternity.
i never let you down
ra-pa-pan-pan-pan (ayy)
gotta be kidding me クセになるでしょ？
Gotta be kidding me, it's getting addictive, right?
ra-pa-pan-pan-pan (ayy)
no love's killing me 足りないのよ oh no
No love's killing me, it's not enough, oh no!
yes! dark breath
感じるでしょ 運命的な衝動を
can you feel it? This fateful impulse!
it's god's breath 脳内細胞 酔わせて
It's God's breath, intoxicating brain cells.
ra-pa-pan-pan-pan 時代 未来なら 繰り出す
ra-pa-pan-pan-pan, if it's the era or future, I'll carve it out.
意外じゃない i'm a genius 全知全能 like a jesus
Not surprising, I'm a genius, omnipotent like a Jesus,
巻き起こす
stirring it up!
(huff-n-puff)
待ちわびてたんだ 導くの全て i'm sorry
I've been waiting for this, guiding everything, I'm sorry.
誰もが羨む 桃源郷へと i'll change it
To a shangri-la everyone envies, I'll change it!
(you'll be crazy, crazy in love)
天才の常套手段は きっと 凡才にはspecialね
A genius's usual tactics are surely special to ordinary people.
誰にも気付かれないけれど 手に入れるわ
Though no one notices, I'll get my hands on it!
ra-pa-pan-pan-pan (ayy)
gotta be kidding me クセになるでしょ？
Gotta be kidding me, it's getting addictive, right?
ra-pa-pan-pan-pan (ayy)
no love's killing me 足りないのよ oh no
No love's killing me, it's not enough, oh no!
yes, dark breath
感じるでしょ 普通じゃない 相当
can you feel it? It's not normal, quite a lot,
it's god's breath 第六感 を澄ませて
it's God's breath, clarifying the sixth sense.
ra-pa-pan-pan-pan
長い長い闇をさまよって 笑い声も忘れてしまった
Wandering through the long, long darkness, I even forgot how to laugh.
悲劇のストーリーが 私の心 狂わせる
A tragic story drives my heart crazy!
ra-pa-pan-pan-pan (ayy)
gotta be kidding me クセになるでしょ？
Gotta be kidding me, it's getting addictive, right?
ra-pa-pan-pan-pan (ayy)
no love's killing me 足りないのよ oh no
No love's killing me, it's not enough, oh no!
yes! dark breath
感じるでしょ 革命的な存在を
can you feel it? This revolutionary existence!
it's god's breath 滞る感情 吹き払って
It's God's breath, blowing away stagnant emotions.
ra-pa-pan-pan-pan 真実 見えないが
ra-pa-pan-pan-pan, truth cannot be seen, but
限界境界灯火 始まります
the limit-border beacon begins!
so 寿命が足りないが
So life span isn't enough, but
今はただ 織り成すを掲げている
right now we just hold up what we weave together.
mara-na-ra-na-na
na-ra-na-ra-na-na
仕方ねえ
Can't be helped.
まだまだ行くぞ！
We're still going!
エリザベス・ローズ・ブラッドフレイム
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
ジジ・ムリン
Gigi Murin
セシリア・イマーグリーン
Cecilia Immergreen
ラオーラ・パンテーラ
Raora Panthera
don't, don't know me, unpredictable
takin' you all below, takin' you all be—
don't, don't know me, irresistible
takin' you all below, below we go
they think they want it? (huh?)
they wanna ge-get down
we take 'em down, down, down
queendom in the borderline run it, no surprise
you ain't gonna win but you can try
told ya, you got no luck
end up in my lineup, listen, listen
run, oh, hide and scream out, already locked ya up
fool's games you always play call me corrupt, won't hear anything
aiming my sight down right on your heart throw in' the keys out, shut down, i-i-i
Aiming my sight down right on your heart, throwing the keys out, shut down, i-i-i.
(justice) love it, the forbidden
(just like that) you're never forgiven
(justice) not one to just forget
(get, get that) we got 'em
the higher i rise, down further you dive
standin' on the edge, don't know me, unpredictable, typical, you
本能が狂い始める
Instincts start to go crazy
追い詰められたハツカネズミ
Like a cornered mouse
今、絶望の淵に立って
Now, standing in an abyss of despair
踏切へと飛び出した
You jump into the railroad crossing
そう　君は友達
Yes, you're my friend
僕の手を掴めよ
So take my hand
そう　君は独りさ
Yes, you're alone
居場所なんて無いだろ
You've got nowhere to go, do you?
二人きりの疵
Sharing our mutual wounds
愛し合えるさ
We're able to love each other
繰り返すフラッシュバック？蝉の声？
A repeating flashback? Cicadas buzzing?
二度とは帰らぬ君
And you, who will never return
永遠に千切れてく
Torn apart for all eternity
お揃いのキーホルダー
Our matching keychains
夏が消し去った
That summer erased away
白い肌の少女に　哀しい程取り憑かれて仕舞いたい
Wanting to be so tragically possessed by the pale girl
本能が暴れ始める
Instincts start to break loose
九月のスタート告げるチャイム
At the start of September, announced by chimes
次の標的に置かれた花瓶
A flower vase placed on the next target
仕掛けたのは僕だった
And the one who started it was me
そう　君が悪いんだよ
It's true, you're the one to blame
僕だけを見ていてよ
Just look at me and me only
そう　君の苦しみ
It's true, you want someone to help you
助けが欲しいだろ
Don't you?
溺れてくその手に　そっとキスをした
I gently place a kiss on your drowning hands
薄笑いの獣たち
Those faintly smiling beasts
その心晴れるまで
Until their hearts are refreshed
爪を突き立てる
Dig their nails into you
不揃いのスカート
And now your skirt is uneven
夏の静寂を切り裂くような悲鳴が
A scream that cuts through the summer silence
木霊する
Echoes through
教室の窓には青空
In the window is the blue sky
そう　君は友達
Yes, you're my friend
僕の手を掴めよ
So take my hand
そう　君が居なくちゃ
Yes, if you're not here next to me
居場所なんて無いだろ
There's no one else where I can be
透き通った世界で
If in this crystal-clear world we see
愛し合えたら
We could share our love, you and me
繰り返す
It repeats again
フラッシュバック？蝉の声？
A flashback, the buzzing cicadas
二度とは帰らぬ君
And you, who will never come back
永遠に千切れてく
Torn apart for all eternity
お揃いのキーホルダー
Our matching keychains
まずじゃあ自己紹介しようか。
First, let's do our self-introductions.
そうだね。
That's right.
おっ！みんな！監査め！
Wow! Everyone, look at this!
元気！滝の空でーす！
Energetic! It's Tokino Sora!
ホロライブ5期生、いや、カバ株式会社...
Hololive 5th Generation, no, Cover Corp...
オレンジ色担当5期生、ねぽらぼのね！みんなの心の...
Orange representative 5th Gen Nepolabo Nene! Everyone's heart's...
最高だももすずねねでーす！よろしくね！
The greatest Momosuzu Nene! Nice to meet you!
おっ、すごい。すごいね。
Oh, amazing. That's amazing.
ていうか、ねねとぬんのペア珍しくない？
I mean, Nene and Nun's pair is pretty rare, right?
本当だ！珍しいよね！
True! It is rare!
だって最戦にねっ娘いるじゃん、ねっ娘いるじゃん！
Because Nekko is right at the front!
あ、そらとものさんも見えてるよ！
Ah, Sora-tomos are visible too!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
今日は、何？なんと、なんと2日目！
Today is what? Amazingly, it's day two!
そうだね！昨日からだから、2日目だ！いえーい！
That's right! Since yesterday, it's day two! Yay!
え、昨日から連日来てきているって人ー！
Um, who's been coming every single day since yesterday?
おー！めっちゃいる！めっちゃいる！
Oh! There are so many!
かなりいる！いつも来てくれてありがとうございます、本当に！
Quite a few! Thank you so much for always coming!
今日初めて来た人ー！
Who came for the first time today?
はい、いっぱいいる！
Yeah, there are lots!
本当にみんな嘘ついてない？
Seriously, you guys aren't lying, right?
いや、昨日から来てる気分の人もいるかもしれない。あ、そうだよね！気分大事、大事！
Well, some might feel like they've been coming since yesterday. Mood is important!
というわけでね、今回のフェスのテーマは「ライディンオンドリームス」ということでね。
So, this festival's theme is "Riding on Dreams".
みんなとかけはしの形があったじゃん？トロッコっていうやつが。トロッコすごくなかった？分かったね！みんなの近くに行ったよ、見えたかな？
There was a bridging shape, right? The Torokko. Wasn't it amazing? Did you see us close by?
え、じゃあ今日のハッシュタグについてちょっとおさらいしていきたいと思います。ハッシュタグは...
Um, let's review today's hashtag. The hashtag is...
This is EXPO!
二六、ホロライブDay2です！
26th, Hololive Day 2 is here!
皆さんたくさんポストしてください！
Everyone, please post a lot!
確かに。
That's right.
じゃあ、何々？ちょっと聞いてみようかな。
So what? Let's try asking them.
日本のみんなー！
Everyone in Japan!
海外にー！
Overseas!
すごい！いろんなところから来てくれてるよー！
Amazing! People came from all over!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
うれしいねー！
We're so happy!
みんなと喋る時間だから！
It's time to talk with everyone!
こんなにたくさんの人の前でスケベができることなんて
Being able to flirt in front of so many people
なかなかないからさ。そうそうそういう意味だったのね。
doesn't happen often. Ah, so that's what you meant.
全然傷つかなかった。
It didn't hurt at all.
タッチさせてよ。
Let me touch you.
何を？触っていい？
What? Can I touch?
あ、あ、もぼぼぼぼ…
Ah, mo-bo-bo-bo...
最高な気分だみんな！
We're in a great mood, everyone!
みんなも楽しんでるかー！
Are you all having fun too?!
え、せっかくさ、私たちさ、MC一番目じゃん。
Since we're the first MC slot,
ね、最初のMC任されちゃったそうだよ。だからもうみんながやりそうなこと全部やっちゃおう。
we're in charge of the very first one.
So let's just do everything.
コーラスからやっちゃおう、やっちゃおう。
Let's do the chorus right from the start!
でね、コーラスで、ぬんにぴったりのやつ考えたから。なんかある？
I thought of something perfect for the chorus.
Got any ideas?
ぬんは今日も？って聞いたら、みんながぬんぬんって返す。
If I ask "Is Nuun today too?",
everyone replies "Nuun-nuun!"
普通になんか、私やりそうな気がしたんだよね。ちょっとやってみよう、やってみよう。
Somehow I felt like doing that.
Let's try it out!
もう一回言って。ぬんは今日も？ぬんは今日も？で
Say it again. "Is Nuun today too?"
"Is Nuun today too?" And then—
あ、オッケーオッケーオッケー。行くよー！
Ah, okay, okay, okay. Here we go!
ぬんは今日もー！
Nuun is here today too—!
ぬんぬーん！
Nuun-nuun!
ペンライトもみんな青色で統一してくれて。ありがとう！
Everyone unified their penlights in blue too. Thank you!
え、ねねちは何にする？どうしようか。
Nenechi, what will you do? What should we do?
ねねは今日も、ねねは今日もー。
Nene is today too, Nene is today too—
なんだろう？え、これどこまでふざけていいんだろ。
What is it? How far can we mess around?
え、いいんじゃない？100パーふざけよ、100パーふざけよ。
It's fine, right? Let's be 100% silly!
え、じゃあねねは今日もっていったら、
So if Nene says "Nene is today too,"
なんて言ってほしいの？なんて言ってほしい？
what do you want them to say?
え、うんぴぴとかあり？それ自分的ありなの？
Unpipi? Is that okay for you?
ありあり、ありなんだ。じゃあ海外にー、エブリバディセイ！
Yeah, it is. Then, everybody say—!
うんぴぴ、レッツゴー！行くよー！
Unpipi, let's go! Here we go!
ねねは今日もー！
Nene is today too—!
言ってくれたー！
They said it!
最高、最高だよー！
It's the best, simply the best!
ねね、こんなにたくさんの人の前でこれ言うのはずかしい！
Saying this in front of so many people is embarrassing!
なに言ってんだろ。めちゃくちゃ嬉しそうだったじゃん今。やったーみたいな。
What is she saying? She looked super happy just now!
え、あれもやろ、あれ。なに？ウェーブ。
Hey, let's do that too. What? The wave.
あ、ウェーブやろう。どっちから行く？こっちから、こっちから、スタンバイ、スタンバイみんな！
Let's do the wave. From here, stand by everyone!
ウェーブ、やりましょう。ウェーブやるよ！
Let's do the wave. We're doing the wave!
せーの！
Ready, set!
戻ろう！戻ろう！まだついてきてないみんなが。戻ろう！
Let's go back! Some people haven't caught up yet!
完璧だみんな！
You guys are perfect!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
みんなでもここでね、あの、お知らせしなきゃいけないことがあるの。
Everyone, there's something we need to announce here.
そうなんだよね、ちょっとあるんだよね。
That's right, there is.
えってもう言われてる。何も言ってないのにもうって言われた。
People are already saying "Eh?" Even though I said nothing!
みんな察しがいいね。
You guys catch on so fast.
察しがいいね！
You really catch on fast!
じゃあぬんちょっと大事なお知らせ…
So Nuun, an important announcement...
あ、そっか、それは私なんだ。
Ah, right, that's me.
いいよ、で。
Go ahead, then.
YouTube、TikTokでご覧の方は、ここまでになってしまいます！
For those watching on YouTube or TikTok,
this is where we leave you!
なんでこうなるのー！
Why does it end here?!
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは、概要欄、概要、概要、概要欄から…
For everyone who wants to keep the hype going,
check the description box...
どこにあるかかんないけど、概要欄からぜひ、配信最短に危険！
I don't know where it is, but please check
the description box to watch the stream live!
というわけで、チラ見せはここまで！せーの、
And with that, the sneak peek ends here! Ready, set,
ライヴ・アン・ドリーム！
Live & Dream!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.